applematters.com 2010-06-23

# Privacy - AppleMatters

What follows is the Privacy Statement for Apple Matters.com

Please read this statement.  
If you have questions please contact us. ****

### Email Addresses

You may choose to add your email address to our contact list as a member of Apple Matters. We agree that we will never share you email with any third party and that we will remove your email at your request. We don't currently send advertising via email, but in the future our email may contain advertisements and we may send dedicated email messages from our advertisers without revealing your email addresses to them. If you have any problem removing your email address please contact us.

### Ownership of Information

Apple Matters is the sole owner of any information collected on our website.

### Comments/Message Boards

If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete comments and forum posts at our discretion.

### Cookies

Currently we assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing this website is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

### Third Party Cookies

****Many of our advertisers use cookies in order to determine the number of times you have seen an advertisement. This is done to limit the number times you are shown the same advertisement.

### Traffic Reports

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

### Business Transitions

If Apple Matters is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our website, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm. ****

### Links

****Apple Matters frequently links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site's privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Apple Matters. ****

### Notification of Changes

****When Apple Matters makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here. ****

### Contact Information

****If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
